

DUDIN OLEKSANDR

Designer with more than 5 years of experience in analyzing various types of interactions and designing interfaces for web graphics, web and applications.

I develop complex projects (websites, landing pages, applications). I also have more than 10 years of experience in graphic, industrial, and interior design. I have a good understanding of the basics of printing, document layout, infographics, and illustrations.

CONTACTS:

+380 (93) 913 85 19 alexdudin16031991@gmail.com

www.dud.in.ua www.linkedin.com/in/oleksandrdudin www.instagram.com/lexdudin

LANGUAGES:

- Ukraine (Native)
- English (Intermediate)

SOFT SKILLS:

- · Communicability & Collaboration
- Weighing the pros and cons of decisions
- · Time management and flexibility
- · Sell the solution
- Appropriateness, stable perception
- Critical thinking
- Self-creativity
- Responsibility
- Feedback
- Argumentation
- Analytical thinking and logic
- Creating new things
- Empathy
- Helping and mentoring

HARD SKILLS:

- Academic drawing (by hand + graph.tablet)
- Coloring and typography
- Polygraphy (product from "0" to production)
- Technologies of interaction processes
- Soft Pack (Figma, Sketch, Adobe Pack)
- Guides and creation of design system
- Video making
- Presentation
- Structuring
- Sense of taste
- Creativity

EXPERIENCE:

Product designer (UI/UX)

Blackshield Capital

Jul 2019 - Present

- · Communication with operational resources and project stakeholders
- Good understanding of UX/UI fundamentals & best practices (research, prototyping, accessibility)
- · In-depth analysis, hypothesis development, information architecture development
- Testing and prototyping (cooperation with QA)
- · Communication with developers, development of technical specifications
- Process tracking (step-by-step support)
- · Creation of system design and guidelines for the company
- · Continuous learning, keeping up with current trends and mentoring

Designer (web & graphic)

<u>Firelink</u>

Jan 2019 - Jun 2019

- Create design documentation (branding, documents)
- Interface rendering in graphics software
- · Work and Collaborate closely with project managers, product team
- Design complex projects (web sites, landings, app)
- Develop new Design Guidelines for work, making workshops for web team
- Experience in analysis, interaction, and interface design for web and mobile app
- Create prototypes or low-fidelity wireframes
- Style design, creating guides to fonts, colors, and sizes
 Manage communication with clients

Lead designer (web & graphic)

Kreston GCG

Jun 2016 - Nov 2018

- Create design documentation (branding, documents)
- Design complex projects (web sites, landings, app)
- Style design, creating guides to fonts, colors, and sizes
- Interface rendering in graphics software
- · Work and collaborate closely with design department and outsourcing
- Manage communication with clients

Designer (web & graphic)

<u>SA-BO-NA</u>

Aug 2014 - May 2016

- Creating concepts and generating new design solutions
- Collection of data on the project and audience
- Style design, creating guides to fonts, colors, and sizes
- · Interface rendering in graphics software

EDUCATION:

2008 NAU (National Aviation University) - Faculty of Architecture & Design

Sep 2008 - Feb 2014

- Bachelor`s degree in design interior & constructing
- Master`s degree in design interior & constructing

COURSES:

PROJECTOR — CREATIVE & TECH ONLINE INSTITUTE

- Mobile Apps Design
- Product Design
- UX Design. Basic

SKILL UP

• 2d Art